Guide to the Time Inc. Time Publishing and Business Records 1929-1999 MS 3009-RG 24
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Promotion and Public Affairs Department Records, 1955-1999; 155.1 Linear feet in 156 record cartons, 1 document case, and 2 flat boxes
  - Subseries IV.A. Director Robert Sweeney Files, 1955-1969, 1981; 8 Linear feet in 9 record cartons
    - Subsubseries III.A.1. Director Administrative Files, 1967-1969, 1981; 3.5 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
      - Indonesian Investment Conference Book Mailing, 1968 (Offsite-box 3052, Folder 5)
      - INSEAD (European Institute of Business Administration), 1968 (Offsite-box 3052, Folder 6)
      - Institute on Man and Science Seminar, 1968 (Offsite-box 3052, Folder 7)
      - Institute of World Affairs, 1968 (Offsite-box 3052, Folder 8)
      - Larsen, Roy: Minneapolis Cocktail Party, 1968 (Offsite-box 3052, Folder 9)
      - Laybourne, Larry: Farewell Party, 1967 (Offsite-box 3052, Folder 10)
      - Lee, Kuan Yew (Prime Minister of Singapore) Meeting, 1968 (Offsite-box 3052, Folder 11)
      - Linen, James: The Journalist Article, 1968 (Offsite-box 3052, Folder 12)
      - Luce, Henry: Memorial, 1968 (Offsite-box 3052, Folder 13)
      - "Making of a President" Political Panel, 1968 (Offsite-box 3052, Folder 14)
      - Managers' Meeting, 1968 (Offsite-box 3052, Folder 15-17)
      - Menswear Fashion Forecast, 1968 (Offsite-box 3052, Folder 18)
      - Montauk Meeting (Public Affairs Department Meeting), 1968 (Offsite-box 3052, Folder 19)
      - National College Presidential Primary (Choice 68), 1968 (Offsite-box 3052, Folder 20-21)
      - National College Presidential Primary (Choice 68), 1968 (Offsite-box 3053, Folder 1-3)
      - Pleva, Jan: Visit, 1968 (Offsite-box 3053, Folder 4)
      - Public Affairs Council, 1968 (Offsite-box 3053, Folder 5)
      - Reunion Dinner for Newstour Participants, 1968 (Offsite-box 3053, Folder 6-8)
      - Russia Newstour, 1968 (Offsite-box 3053, Folder 9)
      - Sales Meeting, 1968 (Offsite-box 3053, Folder 10)
      - Shepley, James: Publisher Dinner, 1968 (Offsite-box 3053, Folder 11-13)
        Includes audiovisual material.
        1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container: "Fuerbringer - Grunwald - Keough Dinner. 6/18/68. 11:00 P.M."
      - Shepley, James: Thank Yous, 1967 (Offsite-box 3053, Folder 14)
        Every year the Time publisher sent out a New Year's thank you note to constant sources of information.
      - Sidey, Hugh: Film, 1968 (Offsite-box 3053, Folder 15-16)
        1 film reel (Compco Corp.); 16mm. Eastman Kodak Company container. On container: "2. Hugh Sidey."
      - Silver Anvil Awards, 1968 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 1)
      - Thomason, James: Retirement Party, 1968 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 2-4)
      - Westerfield, Putney: Promotion Dinner, 1968 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 5)
      - General: 1969 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 6)
      - Bankers Public Relations and marketing Associations Convention, 1969 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 7)
      - China Relations, 1969 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 8)
      - Communications Conference, 1969 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 9)
      - Eisenhower Fellows, 1969 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 10)
      - Managers Meeting, 1969 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 11)
      - March of Time Revival, 1969 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 12)
      - Publicity, 1969 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 13)
      - Steele, John: European Trip, 1969 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 14)
      - Student Press Association, 1969 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 15)
      - Newstour: Update on America '81: Draft Binder, 1981 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 16)
    - Subsubseries III.A.2. Director Event Files, 1964-1967; 1.5 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
      These files were grouped together by either Time Public Affairs or Time Inc. Archives. The dates and materials overlap with Corporate Publicity Files for Time. Records include event proposals, planning, budgets and finances, guest lists, and itineraries.
      - Airlines Dinner (canceled), 1966 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 17-18)
        This event was going to be a tribute to the air transportation industry as part of Time's 40th anniversary celebrations. It was canceled because it coincided with Boeing's plans for its 50th corporate anniversary.
      - ANPA (American Newspaper Publishers Association?) Party, 1964 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 19)
      - Auer, Bernhard: Farewell Dinner, 1967 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 20-21)
      - College Presidents Conference, 1966 (Offsite-box 3054, Folder 22-25)
      - "Environment of Change" Seminar, 1966 January (Offsite-box 3055, Folder 1-12)
        The proposal for this seminar states that a prior seminar with the same title was held in Sterling Forest, NY in 1964. The January 1966 seminar was again held in Sterling Forest at the Onchiota Conference Center. These new seminars were planned in collaboration with Columbia University's Technology and Social Change steering committee. The September 1966 seminar was at Airlie House in Virginia, at the time associated with George Washington University.
      - "Environment of Change" Seminar, 1966 September (Offsite-box 3055, Folder 13-34)
      - Time Ad Sales Meeting: General, 1966 April (Offsite-box 3055, Folder 35-37)
      - Time Ad Sales Meeting: London, 1966 April (Offsite-box 3055, Folder 38-39)
      - Time Ad Sales Meeting: Madrid, 1966 April (Offsite-box 3055, Folder 40-41)
      - Time Ad Sales Meeting: Paris, 1966 April (Offsite-box 3055, Folder 42-43)
      - Time Ad Sales Meeting: Rome, 1966 April (Offsite-box 3055, Folder 44-46)
    - Subsubseries III.A.3. Corporate Publicity, Life Special Projects, and Time Public Affairs Files, 1955-1969; 3 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
      These files of Robert Sweeney were grouped together, maybe as his early files, and include some from when he was a corporate publicity assistant covering all magazines, when he was creative project director for Life, when he was listed as an assistant to the Time publisher, but signing as part of Public Affairs, and through him officially titled as the director of Time Public Affairs. Possibly Sweeney kept these files with his as he moved around or the files were collated by Time Inc. Archives.
      Records include memoranda to head of corporate publicity James Pitt and director of Life promotion Richard Coffey; memoranda and correspondence with various publicity suggestions; the 25th anniversary issue of Fortune; planning for various events and projects organized by or sponsored by Life; and Sweeney's early files working in public affairs for Time.
      - General: Canadian Club of New York, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 1-2)
      - General: Expense Account, 1963 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 3)
      - General: Ideas from Sweeney, 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 4)
      - General: Personal, 1959 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 5)
      - Fortune, 1955-1957 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 6-8)
      - Life: Alumni Federation of Columbia University, 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 9)
      - Life: Astronauts [RESTRICTED], circa 1961-circa 1968 (Offsite-box R28)
      - Life: Communism Booklet, 1962 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 10)
      - Life: Correspondence, 1962 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 11)
      - Life: Cuba Book Promotion, 1963 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 12)
      - Life: Eichmann, Adolf, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 13-16)
      - Life: Franklin, Bob, 1961 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 17)
      - Life: International Geophysical Year, 1960 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 18)
      - Life: Memoranda, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 19-20)
      - Life: "The Most Memorable Events of 1962", 1963 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 21)
      - Life: "The Music of LIFE", 1963 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 22)
      - Life: National Purpose Project: General, 1959-1961 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 23-26)
        The National Purpose Project was coordinated by the National Recreation Association with a public service grant from Life magazine. Through the participation of various organization, it asked a cross section of American leaders what they thought the national purpose should be. Life also reprinted a series of articles with the same name.
      - Life: National Purpose Program: Clippings, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 27)
      - Life: National Purpose Program: Congress, 1960 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 28)
      - Life: National Purpose Program: Educational Institutions "Doing Things", 1960 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 29)
      - Life: National Purpose Program: Local Chairman's Instruction Kit, 1960 (Offsite-box 3056, Folder 30)
      - Life: National Purpose Program: National Recreation Association, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 3057, Folder 1-2)
      - Life: National Purpose Program: Organizations, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 3057, Folder 3-4)
      - Life: National Purpose Program: Presentation Book, 1961 (Offsite-box 3057, Folder 5)
      - Life: National Purpose Program: Replies from Organizations, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 3057, Folder 6-7)
      - Life: NBC Television Special for 25 Years of Life, 1959-1961 (Offsite-box 3057, Folder 8-14)
      - Life: "Pageantry of Life" Promotion, 1963 (Offsite-box 3057, Folder 15)
      - Life: Promotion Film "The Essential Difference", 1963 (Offsite-box 3057, Folder 16-18)
      - Life: Publicity Reports, 1960 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 1)
      - Life: Telegrams and Teletypes, 1963 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 2)
      - Life: Year-End Issue, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 3-4)
      - Life: Year-End Record Album Promotion, 1963 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 5)
      - Time: Campaign Dinners, 1964 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 6)
      - Time: Civil War Issue, 1959 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 7)
      - Time: Demographic Editions, 1964 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 8)
      - Time: Henry Luce Memorial Service, 1967 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 9-10)
      - Time: "How Much Progress" Mailing, 1964 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 11)
      - Time: Ideas, 1964 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 12)
      - Time: International Conference, 1965 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 13)
      - Time: Leadership Community [empty], undated (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 14)
      - Time: Lunches and Dinners, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 15)
      - Time: Nassau Builders' Meeting, 1965 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 16)
      - Time: Negro [African-American] School Project, 1965 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 17)
      - Time: Newspapers Report, 1965 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 18)
      - Time: Newstour: Time Newstour of Africa, 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 19-20)
      - Time: Newstour: Japanese Businessmen's Tour of U.S., 1965 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 21)
      - Time: Newstour: List of Regrets for European Tour, Life Space Tour and Asia Tour, 1965 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 22)
      - Time: Overseas Press Club Dinner, 1964 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 23)
      - Time: Pittsburgh Office Opening, 1969 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 24)
      - Time: Publicity, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 25)
      - Time: "The Rise of the Cheapies", 1964 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 26)
      - Time: Speech: Auer, Bernhard, 1964 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 27)
      - Time: Williams College Seminar, 1966 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 28)
      - Time Inc.: Advertising Dinner, 1964 (Offsite-box 3058, Folder 29)
  - Subseries IV.B. Public Affairs Manager Irina Bagration Files, 1975-1986; 2 Linear feet in 3 record cartons, 1 flat box
    The Time Inc. department head directories list Irina Bagration as Special Events Manager from 1974 to 1980 and Public Affairs Manager from 1981 to 1983.
    The majority of Irina Bagration's files are in the Events Files from her tenure as Special Events Manager since they were mixed together with files from others in the department. These files are the only of hers found on their own. Some of the exhibition files are from after Bagration left Time Inc., but have been left in place as found.
    Bagration's files document the gift of the Time cover art to the National Portrait Gallery and subsequent special exhibitions of cover art to celebrate Time's 60th anniversary. The exhibitions took place as "Britain 1923-1983: an American View" at GLC Royal Festival Hall in London and as "L'Amerique Regarde la France 1923-1983" at the Centre Georges Pompidou in Paris. Records include brochures, correspondence with public affairs staff at the venues and European press consultant, the art specialists writing the wall text, invitations to the receptions, press releases, press clippings, and slides.
    - Time Cover Art Gift: General, 1975-1978 (Offsite-box 3117, Folder 13-15)
    - Time Cover Art Gift: Dinner and Opening Gala, 1978 (Offsite-box 3118, Folder 1-2)
    - Time Cover Art Gift: Dinner and Opening Gala [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R56)
    - Time Cover Art Shows: General: Brochures, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3118, Folder 3-4)
    - Time Cover Art Shows: General: Slides, 1983 (Offsite-box 3118, Folder 5-6)
    - Time Cover Art Shows: London, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 3118, Folder 7-11)
    - Time Cover Art Shows: Paris, 1979-1986 (Offsite-box 3118, Folder 12-18)
    - Time Cover Art Shows: Paris, 1979-1986 (Offsite-box 3119)
    - Time Cover Art Shows: Paris, 1982? (Offsite-box 3040, Folder 3)
    - Time Cover Art Shows: Paris [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Offsite-box R56)
  - Subseries IV.C. Public Affairs Manager Anne Janas Files, 1986-1992; 8 Linear feet in 8 record cartons
    Anne Janas's files include her records on the planning of public projects and events organized or sponsored by Time magazine.
    Organized into three subseries:
    Subsubseries III.C.1. Event Files
    Subsubseries III.C.2. Exhibition Files
    Subsubseries III.C.3. Project Files
    - Subsubseries IV.C.1. Event Files, 1986-1991; 1.5 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
      Time magazine sponsored the interview series "The Creative Edge: An Exploration of the Arts" presented by New York University's School of Continuing Education and directed by Richard Brown. Interviewees included Arthur Miller, Rudolf Nureyev, Stephen Sondheim, Helen Hayes, Tom Wolfe, Philip Johnson, and Yousuf Karsh.
      In 1989, instead of naming a Man of the Year, Time had an issue for Planet of the Year which had a related a conference and exhibition at the National Aquarium in Baltimore.
      This series is Anne Janas's files on Time's participation in the planning and production of "The Creative Edge" interview series including invitations, correspondence with New York University, and interoffice memoranda; the Environment Conference and photograph exhibition related to the Planet of the Year issue; 1987 and 1990 Man of the Year events; and publicity for the Solzhenitsyn interview.
      - The Creative Edge, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 3019, Folder 1-8)
      - The Creative Edge [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Offsite-box R56)
      - Environment Conference 1989, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 3019, Folder 9-13)
        Includes a packet of "Environmental Issues for 1990" from Senator Al Gore.
      - Environment: Exhibition: "The Environmental Challenge: A Photography Exhibit on Endangered Earth", 1990 (Offsite-box 3019, Folder 14-17)
      - Environment: Program of Initiatives at Time Inc., 1989 (Offsite-box 3019, Folder 18)
      - Environment: Publication: "Planet of the Year: Endangered Earth", 1989 (Offsite-box 3120, Folder 1-2)
      - Jimmy Carter Luncheon, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 3120, Folder 3-6)
        Records include arrangements for this event and photographs of it.
      - Man of the Year 1987 / CNN Special, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 3019, Folder 9-10)
      - Man of the Year 1987 / CNN Special [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R56)
      - Man of the Year 1990: Box Publication and Dinner, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 3120, Folder 9-12)
      - Solzhenitsyn, Aleksandr: Interview, 1989 (Offsite-box 3120, Folder 13)
    - Subsubseries IV.C.2. Exhibition Files, 1988-1990; 2.5 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
      Changing Face of Time was planned to be a traveling exhibition from the Time art collection which whad been donated to the National Portrait Gallery. Time held a private preview, and the 1989 Publisher's Conference had a test exhibition. It isn't clear if the full exhibition traveled as anticipated from 1992 to 1993. The New-York Historical Society expressed interest in being a venue.
      Witness to History: 150 Years of Photojournalism was a traveling photography exhibition organized by Time and sponsored by Eastman Kodak. The exhibition accompanied a special issue of Time and featured 100 photographs from the issue. The exhibition opened in Washington, D.C. and traveled to venues in Washington, Los Angeles, Chicago, Boston, and New York.
      This series is Anne Janas's files on art exhibitions organized by Time. Records include proposals, invitations, correspondence with the partner organizations, and interoffice memoranda.
      - Changing Face of TIME, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 3120, Folder 14-21)
      - Changing Face of TIME, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 3014, Folder 1-2)
      - Changing Face of TIME [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R56)
      - Witness to History: 150 Years of Photojournalism, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 3014, Folder 3-21)
        Records include include checklists, invoices, press clippings, kits and releases, insurance, pamphlets, photographs, and the schedule.
      - Witness to History: 150 Years of Photojournalism, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 3015)
      - Witness to History: 150 Years of Photojournalism, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 3016, Folder 1-2)
        Includes audiovisual material:
        1 videocassette (U-Matic SP). On container label: "Faces in Time 1-12-90."
    - Subsubseries IV.C.3. Project Files, 1988-1992; 4 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
      In the 1988 and 1992 United States presidential election years, Time magazine created and sponsored a student mock election as an education project participated in by students from 50,000 schools. Prior to mock election night (five days before the actual presidential election) Time produced and sent out teaching guides to stimulate classroom discussion on the voting process and current political issues. With participation from HBO, CNN and others, Time staged and televised a live broadcast on C-SPAN of returns from the local and main headquarters manned by students.
      Opinion leader mailings were an effort to call to the attention of targeted opinion leaders articles in Time which point to editorial excellence.
      Records include Anne Janas's files on Time book promotions; the planning and production of student mock elections including correspondence with cooperation organizations, interoffice memoranda, teacher guides, event advertisements, ballots, and results; and a description of the opinion leader mailings strategy.
      - Book Promotion: Massacre in Beijing, 1989 (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 16-17)
      - Book Promotion: Mikhail S. Gorbachev: An Intimate Biography, 1988 (Offsite-box 3045, Folder 18)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: General (Offsite-box 3016, Folder 3-7)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: American Association of School Administrators Awards and Convention, 1989 (Offsite-box 3016, Folder 8-9)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Art Student Awards and Reception (Offsite-box 3016, Folder 10)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Associated Litho (Offsite-box 3016, Folder 11)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Awards, 1989 (Offsite-box 3016, Folder 12)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Ballots (Offsite-box 3016, Folder 13)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Benefits to Time [empty], undated (Offsite-box 3016, Folder 14)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Burston-Marsteller [empty], undated (Offsite-box 3016, Folder 15)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Cooperating Organizations (Offsite-box 3016, Folder 16)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Invitations (Offsite-box 3016, Folder 17)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Invoices/Budget (Offsite-box 3016, Folder 18)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Computer Printouts (Final Votes) (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 1)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Decorations/Construction (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 2)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988?: Floor Plan? (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 3)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Food Service (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 4)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: HBO / Production (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 5)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Insurance and Legal (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 6)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Kirshner, Gloria (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 7)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: List of Sponsors (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 8)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Logistics (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 9)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Mailing Lists (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 10)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: New York City Board of Education (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 11)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Overseas Schools (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 12)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Photographs and Photographic Material (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 13-14)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Planning Binder (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 15)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Press Releases / Publicity (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 16-17)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Printed Material and Samples (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 18-19)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Publication "On Voting" (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 20)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Recommendations Survey (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 21)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Results? (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 22)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Samples of Mailings (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 23)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Students [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R56)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Time Education Program (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 24-25)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: TV Pick-ups (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 26)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Voter Movements / Corporate Participants (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 27)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1988: Worldnet Press Kit (Offsite-box 3017, Folder 28)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Ads (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 1)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: American Association of School Administrators (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 2)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Bell, Carol (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 3)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Brochure (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 4)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Budget (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 5)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Cable Operators (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 6)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: The Campaign Game (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 7)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Community Activity (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 8)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Congressional Quarterly (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 9)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Consultant: Starr, Isidore (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 10)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: Contact List (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 11)
      - National Student/Parent Mock Election: 1992: CNN (Offsite-box 3018, Folder 12)